theluxurycloset.com 2019-12-30

# LC - Buy & Sell - Privacy Policy

#### Disclaimer & Privacy Policy.

The information we collect through our Site helps us provide you with information specific to your needs and interests. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) covers the The Luxury Closet website (the “Site” or “The Luxury Closet”), including any registered domain endings, such as “.com”. Please read below to review our Privacy Policy and the types of information we gather through our Site. In this Privacy Policy, “we”, “us”, “our” and other similar references mean The Luxury Closet and “you” and “your” and other similar references mean a specific user of the Site. By visiting the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We update our business practices, Privacy Policy to keep our sellers and buyers informed about their rights and relationship with The Luxury Closet. By visiting The Luxury Closet, you accept the Privacy Policy, the Cookie Policy and the Terms (for the purposes of this document “Terms” mean what is stated in the Terms and Conditions governing use of, sales and purchases made via the Website). Therefore the customers are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted. This Privacy Policy applies to The Luxury Closet solely and does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or organisations to which we link to and from.

#### Cookie Policy

The cookies that we use help us gather information to enhance your experience. The cookies (mentioned below) policy regarding how we process them is explained in this section.

  1. Customer Preference Cookie: The website stores your information like your preference, location that you provide while registering.
  2. Website Functionality Cookies: These cookies let you use the shopping basket, wishlist etc.
  3. Advertising Cookies: It helps us process our campaigns on the basis your information and measure the effectiveness.
  4. Website Analytics Cookies: These cookies help us analyse our customers’ interaction with the website.

By using our website, you give us a permission to record data and send cookies to your device in order to distinguish you from other users on the website and access them the next time you visit the website. You can disable cookies or delete them from time to time. Disabling cookies may hamper access of some features. Please note that a small amount of information will continue being retrieved from your website for basic functionalities

Server Statistics. We collect general statistics to track user trends on our Site. These statistics include hits to our server, the types of browsers used to access our Site, page views, and navigational patterns. The information that is collected in this manner does NOT provide us with any personally identifiable information about our users. It helps us track “where” our users are coming from. This allows us to pinpoint high traffic areas and determine the most effective ways to communicate with our users. As part of that ongoing analysis, The Luxury Closet also uses devices called “web beacons” to help us identify when emails sent to you have been received and read. In order to prevent the introduction of viruses and hackers into the The Luxury Closet site we may collect information, such as IP addresses, into a log file to be used to identify potential hackers of the The Luxury Closet site.

#### When Does The Luxury Closet Collect Your Personal Information

  * When you register or sign up with us
  * When you interact with us on social media platforms
  * When you purchase or sell items from the website
  * When you respond to surveys
  * When you register for newsletters or other communications from us
  * When you contact us with a query or complaint

#### How Do We Utilize Your Personal Data

At times, we also may ask for your details for authentication purposes. This includes address and telephone number which we use for delivery and pick-up services. All the information combined along with your shopping details and website account details shall be utilized to send you more personalized information and marketing updates or any purposes we may describe when you provide the information or other reasons with your consent. If you have expressed a dissent in sharing the personal information that is required, we might not be able to provide you all the services you have asked for. Please note that we keep all the data anonymous.

#### Correcting Your Information

You can correct, delete, alter or express concerns regarding your information by emailing us at [info@theluxurycloset.com](mailto:info@theluxurycloset.com). However, we may not entertain the change or alteration of the data if it is believed to be incorrect or violate the laws.

#### How We Treat Your Personal Data

Sometimes, we share your information with trusted third parties which include delivery couriers, direct marketing companies, Google/ Facebook, IT companies supporting the website etc.

These information are regulated by policies to keep your data safe and protected. We provide your data to the third party to perform a particular service. The amount of data provided would only be as much it is mentioned in our contract with them and no more. At any given point, if you stop using our services, the information is either removed or held anonymous.

Besides, in case of fraud management under certain circumstances, we may share our system information with law enforcement bodies, police or other regulatory or Government bodies.

#### Opt-In, Opt-Out Provision

During the time of registration, we explicitly ask you if wish to subscribe to our offers and information. Once you agree, you are signed up for the following information:

  1. E-mails and alerts for new products and update about new introduction, of any kind from us.
  2. Regular e-mails about offers, products, events and other promotional information and alerts.
  3. Please note that at any given time, you have an option of unsubscribing from the list through our e-mails that contains automated unsubscribe link.

#### Protection Of Your Personal Information

We are committed strictly safeguard your personal information to ensure the integrity and privacy of your data stored by us. We secure your information through special encryption methods to protect it from unauthorised use. Besides, we also ensure that the third parties we share information with have sufficient mechanisms to keep safe your information that we provide.

#### Does the Luxury Closet store Credit Card details on the site?

Credit Card details are not stored our database or server, and are processed through a secure SSL environment.

#### Will The Luxury Closet Disclose The Information It Collects To Outside Parties?

We may share your personal information with third party vendors who help us provide our services to you, such as email providers, mail houses, shipping firms, companies that provide us with marketing services, and other such third parties, but such sharing is always done pursuant to a contract that requires the third party to protect the confidentiality of such information and which prohibits them from using the information for any other purposes.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information as we believe is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority, to determine your credit status or enable debt collection, initiate legal proceedings to recover losses of or otherwise protect our rights or property, or for insurance claim processing, or to prevent harm to yourself or others.

From time to time, we may make our list of registered The Luxury Closet users available for use by select third-party companies whose products or services we believe may be of interest to our registered users. These third-party companies are only permitted to send limited email or postal mailings to our registered users regarding the company’s products or services. Our users’ contact information is provided to a company who manages this process and arranges for the messages to be sent, and is not provided to the third-party advertiser. If you prefer to have your name withheld from receiving email and postal mail from these third-party advertisers, please contact us at customerservice@theluxurycloset.com and let us know.

Lastly, in the event we merge with another company, or we or our assets are acquired by another company, your personally identifiable information would likely be among the assets transferred or shared with such other company. We may disclose Personal Information we collect from you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our Site; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public.

Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over, the information these third parties may collect. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy.

#### External Links. Other companies or organizations may have links to their Sites on our Site.

We are not responsible for how these other companies or organizations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide them. If you choose to access a third party Site linked to our Site, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party Sites.

#### Collection Of Information From Children.

The Luxury Closet does not direct any of our content specifically to children. Users of our Site are required to be at least eighteen (18) years old, and any user under 18 is not an authorized user. If we learn that a user is under thirteen (13) years of age, we will promptly delete any Personal Information we have collected about that user.

#### Consent To Processing In The Middle East Countries.

By providing any Personal Information to The Luxury Closet, all users, including, without limitation, users in the Middle East countries, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such Personal Information across international borders in accordance with The Luxury Closet standard operations, including the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the Middle East countries.

#### Communication:

After registration, customers will receive promotional e-mail communication from the Luxury Closet regarding items on the site. Customers will receive transactional e-mails if they engage in any buying or selling transactions with the Luxury Closet.

Promotional e-mails should be expected daily, whereas transactional e-mails are received if a visitor has bought or submitted an item to sell at the Luxury Closet.

All non-transactional e-mails contain a single click unsubscribe link at the bottom. Clicking on this link will unsubscribe the user from all further promotional e-mails.

Every e-mail sent by the Luxury Closet gives the user the ability to unsubscribe, change, edit or remove any information previously provided. Equally, any such communication always allows the recipient to unsubscribe from the relevant service in order not to receive any further messages. Within each e-mail, the user will be able to unsubscribe by clicking on the unsubscribe link. This link will give you the option to unsubscribe completely and edit your information.

#### Questions, Complaints & Inquiry About Policies

Should you need further information regarding the Privacy and Cookie Policy, have a question or want your complaint to be addressed, please write to us at [info@theluxurycloset.com](mailto:info@theluxurycloset.com)

Or call us on:  
Ph: 800 LUX ( 800 589 )

#### Physical address:

Tradelux General Trading LLC  
Novotel Dubai Al Barsha  
API Trio Tower  
Office 901  
PO Box 502626

#### In Summary.

The Luxury Closet is committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected from our Site helps us better understand our market and consumer interests. This allows us to serve our customers and business associates with the level of satisfaction they deserve.
